>> Brian: 好的，现在在 SearchParams.test 中，
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, so
now inside of SearchParams.test,
我们在这里我们要去
which we have up here, we're going to
从反应，导入呈示和
import React from react, import render and
从反应测试库中清除。
cleanup from react-testing-library.
我们要进口宠物
We're going to import pet,
动物，然后繁殖，
animals, and then breeds, and
来自 @frontendmasters/宠物的狗。
dogs from @frontendmasters/pet.
再一次，记住它会知道从哪一个来抓这个。
And again, remember that it's going
to know which one to grab this from.
然后我们要进口
And then we're going to import
searchParams 来自 ../searchParams。
searchParams from ../searchParams.
所以我们需要做的一件事是做反应测试库
So one thing that we need to do here for
react-testing-library is we're gonna
说以后，是 Jest 给我们的函数，清除。
say afterEach, which is the function
that Jest gives us, cleanup.
这只是一个反应测试库的要求
And this is just a requirement
of react-testing-library,
你必须这么做
you just have to do that.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，然后我们在这里做个小测验。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, and
then we're gonna write a little test here.
我们要测试搜索参数
We're gonna test search params.
>> 布莱恩: 这将是一个异步功能，让我们可以等待。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And this is going to be an async
function so that we can do await.
我们会说 const， curly 花括号， getByTestId，
And we're gonna say const,
curly braces, getByTestId,
通过在 SearchParams 上调用呈现给我们的功能。
which is a function given to us,
by calling render on SearchParams.
>> Brian: 因此，这将在 Node， right，它的速度比刚刚好
&gt;&gt; Brian: So this is going to go render it
in Node, right, which is faster than just
尝试将其呈现给 JSDOM 或类似的内容或具有此 Chrome。
trying to render it to JSDOM or something
like that or to have this Chrome.
然后我们就会说
And then we're gonna say
const animalDropdown =
getByTestId("use-下拉-动物") 和
getByTestId('use-dropdown-animal') and
然后我们就会
then we're gonna
say expect(animalDropdown.childen.length). -
say
expect(animalDropdown.children.length).to-
等于(动画长度)。
Equal(animals.length).
我们的意思是我们要去抓他
So what we're saying here
is we're gonna go grab
我们 SearchParams里面的动物下拉列表
the animal dropdown inside
of our SearchParams.
如果我给它猫，鸟和狗，我希望它能有多少种选择呢 ?
And if I give it cat, bird, and dog,
how many options do I expect it to have?
老实说我希望它能有一个 ANIMALS.lengthrength+1 的权利
Well, honestly, I expect it to
have ANIMALS.length+1 right,
因为其中一个也是所有选项
because one of them is
the all option as well.
所以如果我在里面加一个额外的动物
So if I add an extra animal in there,
我预计会有额外的动物在下降
I would expect there to be
an extra animal in the drop down.
所以如果那是不同步的东西或者类似的东西
So if that's something that keeps falling
out of sync or something like that,
这就是我们要测试的东西，这就是你如何做到的。
that's something we want to test,
this is how you'd do that.
> > 布莱恩: 所以我们要做的事情非常快。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So there's something
we have to go do really quick.
我要你去用下拉菜单
I want you to go to use dropdown.
> > 布莱恩: 在这个选择上
&gt;&gt; Brian: And here on this select,
我们只会给它一个数据证明
we're just gonna give it a data-testid.
然后我们就给它和 id 一样的 id
And then we're just gonna give it
the same id as id right there.
我们为什么要这么做
Now, why are we doing that?
嗯，把你的测试逻辑与正常的逻辑解耦是很不错的，对吧 ?
Well, it's good to decouple your testing
logic from your normal logic, right?
所以，是的，这会被呈现给 DOM ，不，不重要。
So, yes, this will get rendered out to
the DOM and, no, it doesn't matter.
但现在我们可以通过一个测试标识来单独地处理这个问题，
But now we can actually individually
address this by a test ID,
这在最后会有帮助的好吗
which is in the end helpful, okay?
>> Brian: 因此，我们现在需要转至 package.json。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So
now we need to go to our package.json.
我们在这儿有个测试
We have a test thing here.
最后，这将会做一些事情，而不是大喊大叫。
And finally this is going to do something
instead of just yelling and exiting.
所以我们要把这个说的好
So we're just gonna make this say jest.
Jest 挺聪明的所以它会想出其他办法
And Jest is quite smart, so it'll
figure out how to run everything else.
现在，我可以说 npm 运行测试。
So now I can say npm run test.
> > 布莱恩: 看起来我们有个错误。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And looks like we had an error.
我们去看看发生了什么
So let's go see what happened.
>> Brian: 找不到数据证明使用 - 下拉 - 动物。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Unable to find
data-testid use-dropdown-animal.
所以让我们去看看为什么会这样
So let's go see why that's the case.
我想我们把数据证明的标识等于使用下拉列表
I thought we put data-testid
id is equal to use-dropdown.
我把它放这儿了吗
And what did I put here?
使用 - 下拉 - 动物。
use-dropdown-animal.
你知道我在这可能没做什么吗
You know what I probably didn't do here?
这就是我的问题第九行
Yep, this is my problem, line 9.
这必须是一个组件 >> Brian: 因此
This has to be a component
&gt;&gt; Brian: So
而不是第 9 行你把它作为一个组成部分
instead on line 9,
you have that as a component.
现在我们再试一次
Now let's try that again.
>> 布莱恩: 酷，现在已经过去了。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Cool, now it passes.
>> 布莱恩: 所以每当我写测试通过的时候，我总是做的第一件事就是，
&gt;&gt; Brian: So whenever I write a test that
pass, the first thing I always do is like,
我得确保这事也失败了对吧
I need to make sure this fails as well,
right?
所以让我们马上开始使用 Droppdown 。
So let's just go into
useDropdown really quick.
对了你知道我们的选择是空的
And right, you know,
we have an empty option right there.
加起来就像三个空的选择对吧
Let's just add like three empty options,
right?
这应该会让它失败。
That should make it fail.
库兹就能再多 3 个了
Cuz then it's gonna have three
more instead of just one more.
听着，我有 11个，我想 9 个。
Lo and behold, it says, hey,
I got 11, and I expected 9.
所以我不太高兴
So I'm not happy about that.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，这是我们好的第一次测试。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So good,
that's our good first test.
我们去写另一个吧
Let's go write another one.
所以在这里的 SearchParams.test 我们会说
So inside of SearchParams.test here,
we're going to say
期望(pet.vereds). toHaveBeenCallled，对吗 ?
expect(pet.breeds).toHaveBeenCalled,
right?
因为一旦这个东西启动就应该叫 API 然后说，哎，
Because as soon as this thing starts up,
it should call the API and say, hey,
这些品种在哪里
where are the breeds?
我想说的是 breedDropdown .
And I'm going to say const breedDropdown.
>> Brian: = getByTestId("use-下拉列表" )。
&gt;&gt; Brian: =
getByTestId('use-dropdown-breed').
我得说
And I'm gonna say,
期望(breedDropdown.childen.length)toEq- ual(_breeds.length )
expect(breedDropdown.children.length)toEq-
ual(_breeds.length
+ 1)，对吧 ?
+ 1), right?
因此，如果它从 API 中返回 5 ，那么它应该有 6 个选项。
So, if it gets back 5 from the API,
it should have six options.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，让我们给它一个镜头。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So let's give that a shot.
> > 布莱恩: 看起来我们在这里失败了。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
it looks like we failed here.
所以 pett 品种没被调用
So pet.breeds wasn't called.
> > 布莱恩: 那么，我想知道这是什么。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So, I wonder what this is.
我觉得这好像没有得到正确的模拟
I think this looks like it's
not getting the correct mock.
> > Brian: Cuz 不加入 Frontend Masters。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Cuz it's not
getting Frontend Masters.
我做错什么了吗
Did I spell anything wrong?
__mocks__ > frontendmasters > pet.js。
__mocks__ &gt; frontendmasters &gt; pet.js.
>> 演讲者 2: 应该是 @frontendmasters吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Should
that be @frontendmasters?
> > 布莱恩: 就是这样。
&gt;&gt; Brian: That's what it is.
好吧那我们试试吧
Okay, so let's try that.
> > 布莱恩: 太好了，现在又开始了。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Great, so
now it's passing again.
>> Brian: Cool，这意味着 API 肯定会被调用，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Cool, so that means the API
is definitely getting called, right?
如果我们回到代码里的话
The, if we go back to the code.
>> Brian: 肯定会调用 API 。
&gt;&gt; Brian: The API is
definitely getting called.
然后 API 会把你和你的五种
And the API is then giving back
the five breeds that you and
我是一起列出的对吧
I listed together, right?
那是正确的工作，对吧 ?
And then that is working correctly, right?
那是保证对吧
That's assuring, right?
这就是你想要退出测试的原因
Which is what you want out of your tests.
所以让我们在这里更进一步。
So let's go one step further here.
> > 布莱恩: 在这个电话里我们得多弄几件事
&gt;&gt; Brian: And we have to get a couple
more things out of this call right here.
所以我们要去拿个容器
So we're gonna grab a container and
一个 getTestById ，我们将抓取 getByText。
a getTestById and
we're gonna grab getByText.
getByText ，好吗 ?
getByText, okay?
因此，我们希望首先看到这一点。
So we want to see that
at first it renders.
然后我们要模拟一个点击按钮，对。
Then we're going to simulate
a click on the button, right.
他们将会看到它是否从 API中得到了宠物的帮助。
And they're going to see if it gets
pets back from the from the API.
所以我们会说 const searchResults =
So we're gonna say const searchResults =
getByTestId('search-results') ，和
getByTestId('search-results'), and
我们得马上把它放进来
we'll have to go put this
in here in just a second.
布莱恩: 我们会说
&gt;&gt; Brian: We're gonna say
expect('searchResults.textContent').toEq- ual。
expect('searchResults.textContent').toEq-
ual.
>> Brian: 未找到 Pets 。
&gt;&gt; Brian: No Pets Found.
> > 布莱恩: 然后我们会在那之后说，火焰火。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And then we're gonna
say after that, fireEvent.
> > 布莱恩: 我们也得去拿那个，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: And we'll have to go get that,
as well, right?
>> 布莱恩: 所以我们要从反应测试库中自动导入。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So we're gonna auto-import
that from react-testing-library.
>> Brian: 因此，我们会说 getByText('Submit')，所以
&gt;&gt; Brian: So
we're gonna say getByText('Submit'), so
我们要去找 " 提交 " 按钮 Submut 我能拼
we're gonna go find the Submit button,
Submut, I can spell.
提交，我们会给它一个新的点击鼠标事件。
Submit, and we're gonna give
it a new MouseEvent of click.
>> 布莱恩: 好的，所以你知道，我从
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, so just so you know,
I imported that fireEvent from
2 号线路的反应测试库
react-testing-library right
there in line 2.
> > 布莱恩: 我们会说 ( 动物)
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
we're gonna say expect(pet.animal),
动物就像你的哈韦比恩卡莱
animals, as it is, toHaveBeenCalled.
所以我们预期它会进入 API。
So we're expecting it to go to the API.
然后我们要去
And then we're going
期望 (searchResults.childen.length).toE-
to
expect(searchResults.children.length).toE-
qual(_dogs.length)。
qual(_dogs.length).
现在我们有个小问题
Now, we have a minor problem here.
次要的问题是方法
The minor problem is that the method to
请求宠物不会像个异步的人一样工作
request pets won't work as an async await,
这是我们第一次执行它的方式
which is how we implemented
it in the first place.
没有什么好办法让我们跟猴子以外的人合作
And there's not really a good way for us
to work around that with other than monkey
修修补补如果这听起来很吓人的话
patching promises,
which if that sounds scary to you,
因为它是这样我们不会这么做的
that's because it is, and
we're not gonna do that.
所以为了这个特定的文本，
So for the sake of this
particular text right now,
我要去改变这个在 SearchParams中实施的方式。
I'm just going to go change how this
is implemented in SearchParams.
这是一个异步函数，它并不是真正地给我们买那么多。
So here this is an async function, and
it's not really buying us that much.
我们只会说功能宠物我们只会说动物
We're just gonna say function pet,
and we're just gonna say pet.animals.
然后我们就把这个放进去吧
And then we're just gonna put
this inside of .then animals.
> > 布莱恩: 把 setPets 移到这里，去掉这个。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And move setPets into here,
and get rid of this.
>> 布莱恩: 所以我所做的只是把它作为原始的承诺
&gt;&gt; Brian: So all I did was just
re-implement this as raw promises instead
正在使用异步 / 等待。
of using async/await.
我和一个在 Facebook 工作的人进行了一段时间的对话
And I had an at length conversation with
someone that worked at Facebook about this
我们能不能这样做
like, can we not do this?
他们基本上说他们不想
And they basically said,
they're trying not to,
因为 Facebook 到处都在等待
because Facebook has
async/await everywhere.
他们也想这样做
And they wanna do this as well.
但现在，这就是你如何使用异步等待和测试的方式。
But for now, this is how you kinda use
async await and test at the same time.
>> Brian: 我们确实需要快速的进入到  。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And we do have to go
into results.js really quick.
> > 布莱恩: 在这类搜索的分类上，我们要给它一个测试标识，
&gt;&gt; Brian: And say here on the className
of search, we have to give it a test ID,
其中数据 - testid='search-results'。
which data-testid='search-results'.
> > 布莱恩: 好吧，现在希望，手指交叉了，那是很多代码。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, now hopefully,
fingers crossed, that was a lot of code.
npm 运行测试，我们应该会有更多的测试通过。
npm run test,
we should get a bunch more tests passing.
我们做到了
And we did.
所以这意味着如果我们回去搜索 test.js，
So that means if we go
back into search test.js,
它最初没有发现任何宠物如果我点击
it's initially rendering no pets found,
and then if I click,
它会调用 API 然后给出正确数量的宠物
it'll call the API and
then given a correct amount of pets,
然后就会调用 API 并返回正确数量的狗。
it's then going to call the API and
get back a correct amount of dogs.
它会让一只宠物
And it'll render one pet for
它们从 API中得到的每一种动物
each one of those animals that
it gets back from the API.